Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- B
  - Burgum, Edwin Berry, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Burke, J. Martin, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Burke, Kenneth, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Burke, Michael, undated (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Burlingame, Lloyd, 1977, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Burman, Jane, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Burneson, Sam, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Burney, Bill, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Burnham, James, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Burnham, Robert, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Burns, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Burns, Bonnie, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Burns, Eveline M., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Burns, Gerald P., 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Burns, Sarah, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Burns, Red, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Burrow, James, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Burrows, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Burrows, Abe, undated (Box 118, Folder 36)
  - Burrows, Alieina, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Burstyn, Ellen, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Burton, Angela, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Buscemi, N. Paul, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bush, Carlton, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Busse, Alvin C., undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Bustin, Raul, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Butcher, Earl O., 1964, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Buteux, Raymond D., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Butler, Benjamin F., undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Butler, Charles R., undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Butler, L. Carolus, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Butler, Octavea, undated (Box 118, Folder 37)
  - Butler, Ralph Starr, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Buttenwieser, Helen, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Buttimore, Dennis I., undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Buzzeo, Michael, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Byrd, Richard E. (Admiral), 1930 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Byrne, John, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Byrnes, Joseph A., 1976, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- C
  - Cabrera, Tony, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Cadoff, Irving B., 1968 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Caesar, Joel, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Cahn, Edward, 1957, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Cain, Juliet, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Calamia, undated (Box 118, Folder 38)
  - Calderone, Mary, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Caldwell, Amanda, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Caldwell, Paulette, 1988, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Caldwell, Sarah, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Caldwell, Zoe, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Calhoun, Craig, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Califanco, Joseph, 1988, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Callahan, North, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Callender, Maurice and Stan, undated (Box 118, Folder 39)
  - Callman, Ellen, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Camajo, Jackie, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Camberlin, Tish, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Camera, Joan, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cameron, Eric, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cameron, John C., undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Cameron, Kenneth N., 1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Camey, George, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Camino, Liz, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Campanis, Alexander, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Campbell, Bruce, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Campbell, Harold, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Campbell, Les, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Campbell, Marian, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Campbell, Mary S., 1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Campbell, Meredith, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Campbell, Paul, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Cancro, Robert, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Cane, James, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Canemaker, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Canfield, Cass, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Cann, Frank H., undated (Box 19, Folder 23, Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Cann, Howard, 1920, 1933, 1943, 1970
    - Photographs (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 40)
  - Cann, Tedford, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Cannon, Robert, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Cannon, Walter B., undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Cantarella, Eva, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Cantor, Norman, 1978-1982, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Cantrell, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Cao, Jie, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Caplan, Joan, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Caplin, Andrew, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Capote, Truman, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Capozzola, John, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Capozzoli, Tom, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Capponi, Lou, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Caprio, Al, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Carabba, Victor, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Carbonara, E. Vernon, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Carda, Caroline, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Cardasis, James, 1966, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Carducci, Mike, 1944 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Carey, Harry, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Carey, Hugh, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Carey, Larry, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Carey, Pat, 1972, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Cargill, Oscar, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Carillo, Sal, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Carlisle, Kitty, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Carlisle, Robert J., undated (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Carlock, George H., 1959-1979 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Carlock, James G., 1956 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Carlock, Richard B., undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Carlos, King Juan I, 1983
    - Photographs (Box 19, Folder 55, Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 41)
  - Carlsen, Eugene, circa 1933-1935 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Carmen, Whit, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Carmel, Harold, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Carmichael, Hattie M., 1952 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Carmichael, Stokely, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Carne, Margaret, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie, Andrew, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 5, Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Carnesecca, Lou, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Carnevale, Ben L., 1966, 1968
    - Photographs (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 42)
  - Carnevale, Laurence, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Carney, Kim, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Carnicke, Sharon, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Caro, Robert, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Carol, Ed, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Caroli, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Carpenter, T.J., 1945 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Carpentier, Fran, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Carr Hobart, 1956, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Carr, James, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Carra, Lucille, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Carras, William Gabe, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Carreras, Karen, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Carroll, Charles, 1876, 1878, 1883 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Carse, James P., 1974, 1980-1989
    - Photographs (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 43)
  - Carson, Edward G., 1962 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Carson, Leonard A., undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Carter, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Carter, Arthur L., 1988 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Carter, David, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Carter, Jimmy, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Carter, Martin B., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Carter, Richard, undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Carter, Will, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Carter, Zachary, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Cartmel, N.M., undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Carton, Aaron S., 1963 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Cartter, Allan M., 1966-1970 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Carty, Frank, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Caruso, Michael, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Carver, George Washington, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Cary, Edward H., undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Cary, Vivian, undated (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Casadovall, Arturo, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Case, Karen, undated (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Casey, Allen, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Casey, Joanne, undated (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Casey, Thomas F., undated (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Casey, Tom, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Cassan, Lionel I., 1956, 1964, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Cassidy, Eileen, circa 1980s (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Castagna, James, undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Castelli, Arthur, undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Castello, Hugo M., 1962, 1971
    - Photographs (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 44)
  - Castello, James, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Castello, Julio, 1962, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Castiglione, Bob, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Castle, Patrick, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Caston, Ann, undated (Box 118, Folder 45)
  - Casulduero, Joaquín, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Catacosinos, William J., undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Cavallo, Stefan A., undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cavett, Dick, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Cecere, Dominic, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Cecil, James M., undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Cella, Edward, circa 1936 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Cemashko, Fred, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Cendoma, Cynthia, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Cerbone, James, circa 1933 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Cerff, Phyllis, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Cerqui, John, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Cerveny, George, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Cestari, F.G., undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Cestary, Roy, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Chalaire, Walter, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Chalek, Alverne, circa 1940s (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Chalmers, George, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Chalt, Marc, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Chamberlain, Clarence, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Chamberlain, Lucy, 1953
    - Photographs (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 46)
  - Chamberlain, Tish, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Chamberlain, Waldo, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Chambers, Raymond, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Chambers, Robert, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Champion, George, undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Chan, Lisa G., undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Chan, Stephanie, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Chancellor, John, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Chaney, William R., undated (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Chang, Chris, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Chang, Evita, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Chang, Roberto, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Chang, Wejen, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Chang, Young-Tae, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Chaniotis, Angelos, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Channing, Carol, 1980, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Chapin, Albert F., undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Chappell, Andrew, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Charipper, Harry A., 1961, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Charl, Oscar, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Charles, Irene, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Charlety, Sebastien, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Charlton, Craig, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Charry, Jonathan, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Charyn, Jerome, undated (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Chase, Carl T., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Chase, David B., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Chase, Francis Seabury, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Chase, Harry, undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Chase, Harry W., 1933-1951 (Box 21, Folder 54, Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Chase, Lucetta Crum, undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Chase, Oscar, 1990, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Chase, Randolph M. Jr., 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chase, William M., 1923
    - Photographs (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 47)
  - Chasis, Herbert, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Chaudhuri, Una, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Chavart, Carey, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Chavez, Dr., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Chazan, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Cheever, John, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Chein, Isidor, 1961, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Chelkowski, Peter, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Chemmers, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Chen, Greg, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Cheng, Dinoh, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cheng, Mr., 1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Cherico, Gerald, circa 1946 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Cherico, Ross J., undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Cherlasky, Martin, undated (Box 118, Folder 48)
  - Cherry, James, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Chese, Dean, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Chesler, Evan, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Chester, Gulielmus W., 1949 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Cheung, Tan Yee, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Chevigny, Paul, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Chi, Michael, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Chi, Yang Jie, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Chicoye, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Chigbu, John, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Childres, Robert, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Chin, Al, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Chin, Martin, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Chinitz, Barry, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Chioles, John, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Chisolm, David, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Chisolm, Shirley, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Chizik, Efraim, undated (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Choe, Martha, undated (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Choi, Frederick, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Choudhry, Mito, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Choy, Christine, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Choy, Fred, undated (Box 118, Folder 49)
  - Chresteam, Ivey, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Christ-Janer, Albert, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Christ, Judith, undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Christensen, Thomas, 1963, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Christenson, James H., 1980 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Christiansen, undated (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Christophe, Jean, undated (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Chubba, Alice, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Chung, Young Yang, undated (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Church, Austin H., undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Church, Joe, undated (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Church, Robert, undated (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Chute, Charleton, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Cieslak, Alexander, undated (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Ciraco, Orland, undated (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Cisneros, Henry, undated (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Citarrella, Tony, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Clark, A., undated (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Clark, Alfred, circa 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Clark, Bernice W., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Clark, Clarence C., 1957 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Clark, Clifford, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Clark, John H. III, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Clark, Kenneth, 1969, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Clark, Lewis, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Clark, Lincoln M., 1954 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Clark, Ramsey, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Clark, Ray, undated (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Clark, Wallace, undated (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Clarke, Frederick, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Clarkson, Allen, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Claster, Jill, 1979-1984
    - Photographs (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 50)
  - Claxton, Allan E., 1975, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Clay, David M., undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Clay, Sarah, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Clayton, Allen, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Clemen, Alexander, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Clements, Edna, undated (Box 118, Folder 51)
  - Clements, Robert, 1962, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Clifford, James, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Clifford, W.O., undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Clift, Virgil, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Clinton, Bill, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Clinton, Hillary, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Clyne, James F., 1942, 1953, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Cnossen, Sijbren, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Coakley, C.G., undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Coakley, George W., 1938 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Coats, William J., 1939 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Cobb, Henry, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Cogg, Dr. Jewel Plummer, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Cochran, Thomas, 1901 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Cochran, Thomas C., 1942 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Codori, Carol, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Coe, Barbara, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Coe, Henry C., undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Coehn, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Coelho, David H., undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Coen, Joel, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Coes, Kent Day, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Coester-Waljen, Dagmar, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Coffey, Diane, 1983
    - Photographs (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 52)
  - Cogan, Arnie, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Cogan, Marshall, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Cohen, Carl, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Cohen, Carol, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Cohen, Frank J., 1964 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Cohen, George M., undated (Box 118, Folder 53)
  - Cohen, Gerson, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Cohen, Irwin, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Cohen, Jacob, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Cohen, James, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Cohen, Jerome, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Cohen, Joel E., undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Cohen, Liz, 1993, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Cohen, Matthew, undated (Box 118, Folder 54)
  - Cohen, Robert, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Cohen, Steve, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Cohn, Debra, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Cohn, Margot, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cohn, Roy, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cohn, Wendy, undated (Box 118, Folder 55)
  - Colbert, Claudette, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Coldstream, George, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cole, David, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Cole, Gordon, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Cole, Johnetta B., undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Cole, Richard, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Coleman, Beatrice, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Coleman, Jules, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Coleman, Margaret, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Coles, Geraldine, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Coles, Jerome, 1978, 1981
    - Photographs (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 56)
  - Colin, Oscar, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Collier, Georgiana, undated (Box 118, Folder 57)
  - Collingwood, Charles, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Collins, Barbara, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Collins, Daniel, 1969, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Collins, Donald Edward, 1967, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Collins, G. Rowland, 1954, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Collins, Leo V., undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Collins, Lurraine, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Collins, Lynn A., undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Collitano, Joseph, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Colpin, Emmet R., 1943 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Colston, James A., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Columbus, Chris, 1993
    - Photographs (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 58)
  - Colvin, Charles H., 1941, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Combes, Frank C., undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Comden, Betty, 1937 (Box 118, Folder 59)
  - Comden, Betty and Kyle, undated (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Comella, Daniel, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Comfort, Patrick, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Comfort, William, undated (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Comment, Robert, undated (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Commerce, undated (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Compton, Karl T., 1946 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Comyns, undated (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Comyns, Raymond, undated (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Conant, Howard S., 1959, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Conant, Joseph, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Conforti, James Jr., 1961 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Conhill, undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Conklin, Dr. George T. Jr., undated (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Conklin, John, undated (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Conklin, Mary Washburn, undated (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Conlin, James, undated (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Connally, Val, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Connell, Ed, undated (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Connelly, Joan, 1996
    - Photographs (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 60)
  - Connelly, Terry R., undated (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Conners, Jack, undated (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Connery, Joseph E., undated (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Connolly, Michael, undated (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Connolly, Robert, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Connors, Bill, undated (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Consagra, Joseph, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Consilarius, Georgious Griswold, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Contini, Renato, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Conway, Albert, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Conwell, Ed, undated (Box 118, Folder 61)
  - Cook, Paula, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cook, Walter W.S., undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Cooke, Cardinal Terrace, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Cooley, Hollis R., undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Cooley, Rita W., 1963, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Coolidge, Martha, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Coomaraswamy, Radhika, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Coonradt, Arthur C., 1943 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Coons, Edgar, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Cooper, Derrick, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Cooper, Kent, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Coor, Gertrude, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Copeland, Melvin Thomas, undated (Box 118, Folder 62)
  - Coppel, Sylvain, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Corbett, Lily, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Corbin, Arnold, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Corbitt, Ted, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Cordier, Andrew, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Cordy, Neta, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Corfman, Kim P., undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Cork, Walter, undated
    - Photographs (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 63)
  - Cornell, William B., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Corradi, Dr., 1975 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Corradino, Dolph, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Corrigan, Robert W., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Corse, James, undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Coruzzi, Gloria, 1993
    - Photographs (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 64)
  - Corvin, Pamela, undated (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Cosby, Bill, 1994
    - Photographs (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 65)
  - Cosell, Howard, 1974, 1976, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Cosson, L., undated (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Costa, Maria Catarina, undated (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Costello, Hugo, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Costello, Jane, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Costello, Julio, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Costello, Timothy W., 1970 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Costigan, Pat, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Costigan, Peter, undated (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Cott, Betty, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Cotter, William E., undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Cottrell, Leonard S. Jr., undated (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Coughlan, Joseph D., undated (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Courant, Richard, 1958, 1961, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 46, Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Courtadon, Georges, undated (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Coutant, Frank, undated (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Coutts, Alan, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Covi, Davis, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Cowan, Victoria, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Cowley, Malcolm, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cox, Glenn, 1954, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Cox, Kitty, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Cox, Phillip W., undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Cox, Samuel H., undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Cozonis, Daphne, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Crabtree, Pam, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Crafts, Leland, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cragun, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Craig, C. Samuel, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Crane, Gerald C., 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Cravarelli, Vincent, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Craven, Wesley Frank, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Crawford, Barbara, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Crawford, Mark, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Creedon, John J., 1990 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Cricco, Nancy, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Crick, Bernard, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Crincoli, Nicholas, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - "Miss Cripp", undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Crocker, Lawrence, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Crofts, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Croker, Al, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Croly, Jane Cunningham, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Cromer, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Croner, Maie, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Cronin, Janice, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Cronk, H. Taylor, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Cronkite, Walter, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 32)